Shaikh Mohammad Sadique Mushtaque

Bhiwandi Thane Maharashtra 421302 7219871318 sadiques027@gmail.com

Objective

"Motivated and detail-oriented sales professional with five years of supervisory experience seeking a management position. Seeking an opportunity to apply my advanced knowledge of sales and customer service and my experience with team-building and staff development."

Experience

• Airtel Payment Bank

18/06/2018-31/12/2021

RBM PROMOTER

Sales Airtel Payment Bank I'd, Micro ATM And Policy

Paytm Payment Bank

01/01/2022-31/12/2022

FILED SALES EXECUTIVE

Field Sales Executive

Airtel Payment Bank

01/01/2023-Present

KAE SALARY DISTRIBUTION

Salary Distribution

Education

Swayam Siddhi College

B.Com

GPA

Samdiya High'School And Jr College

12th

GPA

Skills

- Sales
- Team management
- Communication
- Leadership

Achievement & Awards

- Best promoter of the year 2020
- 4 time best promoter of the month

Language

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

Interests

- Cricket
- Music
- Field work

Personal Details

• Date of Birth : 12/06/2000

Nationality : India Marital Status : Single

Shaikh Mohammad Sadique Mushtaque